Guy Di Carlo, Jr. Civil War Research Papers, 1862-2002, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Union Corps. (Box-folder 12:30)
- Union Corps—Badges and Medals. (Box-folder 12:31)
- Union Enlisted—General File. (Box-folder 12:32)
- Union Generals—Books and Pamphlets. (Box-folder 12:33)
- Union Generals—General File. (Box-folder 12:34)
- Union Generals—Short Biographies. (Box-folder 12:35)
- Union Soldiers—Photos and Illustrations. (Box-folder 12:36)
- VanDorn, Earl. (Box-folder 12:37)
- Vicksburg, July 4, 1863. (Box-folder 13:1)
- Virginia. (Box-folder 13:2)
- Virginia Cavalcade. (Box-folder 13:3)
- Virginia cities brochures. (Box-folder 13:4)
- Virginia—Booklets and brochures (1 of 3). (Box-folder 13:5)
- Virginia—Booklets and brochures (2 of 3). (Box-folder 13:6)
- Virginia—Booklets and brochures (3 of 3). (Box-folder 13:7)
- Virginia—General brochures. (Box-folder 13:8)
- Virginia—Southern Generals. (Box-folder 13:9)
- Virginia—Maps. (Box-folder 13:10)
- Wade, Benjamin Franklin—Senator, Ohio. (Box-folder 13:11)
- Wallace, Lew. (Box-folder 13:12)
- War of 1812. (Box-folder 13:13)
- Washington, D.C., CWRT. (Box-folder 13:14)
- Washington, D.C.—Forts. (Box-folder 13:15)
- Washington, George. (Box-folder 13:16)
- Weapons—Artillery and Ammunition (Union and Confederate). (Box-folder 13:17)
- Weapons—Rifles, Handguns (Union and Confederate). (Box-folder 13:18)
- West Point. (Box-folder 13:19)
- West Virginia—newspaper articles. (Box-folder 13:20)
- West Virginia—booklets and brochures. (Box-folder 13:21)
- Westwood, Howard C.—Talks. (Box-folder 13:22)
- White House (Washington, D.C.). (Box-folder 13:23)
- Wilderness, Battle of, May 5-7, 1864. (Box-folder 13:24)
- Wilderness, Battle of—Cold Harbor Maps, May 5-7, 1864. (Box-folder 13:25)
- Winchester, 1862-1863. (Box-folder 13:26)
- Wisconsin. (Box-folder 13:27)
- Women. (Box-folder 13:28)
- Letters from Paymaster's Steward John Swift, U.S. Navy. (Box-folder 14:1)
- Information on the Seventy Third Regiment of the Illinois Infantry Volunteers, nicknamed The Preacher's Regiment. (Box-folder 14:2)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1955-September 1959. (Box-folder 14:3)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1960-December 1962. (Box-folder 14:4)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1963-December 1965. (Box-folder 14:5)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1966-December 1967. (Box-folder 14:6)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1968-December 1969. (Box-folder 14:7)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1970-December 1971. (Box-folder 14:8)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1972-December 1973. (Box-folder 14:9)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1974-December 1975. (Box-folder 14:10)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1976-December 1978. (Box-folder 14:11)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1979-December 1981. (Box-folder 14:12)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1982-December 1984. (Box-folder 14:13)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1985-December 1987. (Box-folder 14:14)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1988-December 1990. (Box-folder 14:15)
- Photocopy of Civil War History, March 1991-December 1993. (Box-folder 14:16)
- Civil War Tour slides. (Box 15)
  List of Tour Sites
  Antietam-South Mountain, n.d.
  Brandy Station, Wilderness, Spotsylvania Courthouse, n.d.
  Chancellorsville, n.d.
  Chickamauga, Chattanooga, Stone's River, n.d.
  Ft. Donelson; Tupelo, Mississippi; Brice's Crossroads, n.d.
  Ft. Sumter; Charleston, South Carolina, n.d.
  Gettysburg, n.d. [3 folders]
  First and Second Manassas, n.d.
  Pea Ridge; Prairie Grove, Arkansas, n.d.
  Richmond, Seven Days Battles, 1967-1968
  Shiloh, n.d.
  Vicksburg, n.d.
  Harpers Ferry, South Mountain, 1969
  The Atlanta Campaign, 1971
  Lee's Retreat from Petersburg to Appomattox
  Shenandoah Valley-1862: Jackson-1864: Early, n.d.
  Civil War Cemeteries, n.d.
  Civil War Forts, n.d.
  Abraham Lincoln, Lincoln Conspiracy, Conspirators' Trail, n.d.
  Civil War History in Ohio, n.d.
  Ohio Monuments on Civil War Battlefields, Weapons and Weaponry, n.d.
  Re-enactment Group: Antietam, Gettysburg, Manassas, 1974-1981
  Civil War Washington Landmarks and Buildings, Booth Escape Trail, n.d.
- Civil War Round Table newsletters, Civil War magazines, newspaper clippings, brochures and other war-related printed material, 1954-2003. (Box 16)
- Audio cassettes and Videocassettes, 1952-1995, n.d. (Box 17)
  List of Audio Cassettes
  Beauregard the Man, 1955
  John Wilkes Booth Capture, n.d.
  Chancellorsville Auto Tour, 1979
  Cleveland Civil War Round Table, 1993 [2 items]
  Stephen A. Douglas, 1983
  Ft. Pillow Massacre, n.d.
  Fredericksburg Auto Tour, 1978
  Hard Hand of War, 1996
  Ulysses S. Grant, 1952
  Abraham Lincoln, 1949
  Manassas, n.d.
  Politics and the Army of the Potomac, 1963
  Edwin Stanton, n.d.
  Western Union, 1950
  List of Videocassettes
  Grant's March: the Vicksburg Campaign and Seige, 1995
  Gettysburg, n.d.
  Civil War Battles / Civil War Journal, n.d.
  Great Battles of the Civil War, n.d.
  Touring Civil War Battlefields, 1988
  Civil War (pts. 3-4), n.d.
  Shenandoah, n.d.
  David Herbert Donald, n.d.
- Videocassettes, 1930-2002. (Box 18)
  Abraham Lincoln, 1930
  America's Civil War: 1st Manassas, 1986
  America's Civil War: Vicksburg, 1989
  Antietam: the Bloodiest Day in American History, [1987?]
  Battles of the Civil War, n.d. (2 vols.)
  The Blue and the Gray, 1986 (2 vols)
  Chickamauga: River of Death, [1988?]
  Civil War, n.d. (6 vols.)
  The Civil War, n.d.
  The Civil War, 1991 (2 vols.)
  Civil War Battlefields, 2000
  Civil War Docs, n.d. (3 vols.)
  Civil War Generals, n.d.
  Civil War Journal, n.d. (6 vols.)
  The Civil War Photographers, 1989
  The Civil War: the Story and the Artillery, 1994
  Divided Union: Story of the Civil War, n.d. (2 vols.)
  Echoes of the Blue & Gray: Civil War Veterans on Video Cassette, 1989
  The General, n.d.
  Gettysburg: the Final Fury, 1983
  Gettysburg: The Video History of the Civil War, n.d.
  The Great Campaigns of the Civil War, 1994 (2 vols.)
  History of the Civil War, n.d.
  The Last of Mrs. Lincoln, 1972 / Young Mr. Lincoln, 1939
  Lincoln, 1992 (2 vols.)
  Monocacy: the Battle That Saved Washington, [1989?]
  New Market: Field of Honor, [1989?]
  North and South Book II, 1986. (3 vols.)
  North and South, 1985 (3 vols.)
  Raising the Hunley: The Resurrection of the Civil War Legend, 2002